JUAN DELGADILLO

2215 Costa Palma Ave · 702-927-0816 JCD2567@GMAIL.COM

Substantial experience and outstanding skills in Customer Service, accustomed to working in fast paced environment with the ability to think quickly, work well with others and successfully handle difficult customers. I can be expected to exercise good judgment based on company objectives, adhere to business ethics and fair play. I am bilingual in Spanish, I have experience in keyboarding, Ten-Key and extensive computer knowledge.

EXPERIENCE

09/2008-12/2014

COMPUTER TECHNICIAN, FOUNDATION FOR AN INDEPENDENT TOMORROW (FIT)

- Set up hardware and install and configure software and drivers
- Maintain and repair technological equipment (monitors, routers, printers) or peripheral devices
- Install well-functioning LAN/WAN and other networks and manage components (servers, IPs etc.)
- Manage security options and software in computers and networks to maintain privacy and protection from attacks
- Perform regular upgrades to ensure systems remain updated
- Troubleshoot system failures or bugs and provide solutions to restore functionality
- Arrange maintenance sessions to discover and mend inefficiencies
- Keep records of repairs and fixes for future reference
- Offer timely technical support and teach users how to utilize computers correctly

01/2015 - 07/2017

INBOUND SUPERVISOR, RAKUTEN SUPER LOGISTICS

- Oversee receiving and other warehouse processes and personnel to make sure work
 meet quality standards and is performed according to established procedures. Provide
 training of current and new employees in all appropriate procedures and processes
 required to complete work assignments.
- Provided daily work assignments to staff and worked with managers and other supervisors to coordinate personnel and resources as necessary to complete all work scheduled for the department.
- Operated lift trucks, pallet jacks, and other equipment to safely move parts to proper locations and load and unload trucks, as necessary. Observed the receipt of purchased goods verifying counts and quality, completed transactions to receive product, processed paperwork and completed all necessary transactions according to established procedures.

07/2017-09/2018

RECEIVING COORDINATOR/ SHIPPING COORDINATOR, CJ PONY PARTS

- Worked with the Director to develop strategies and objectives to maximize productivity
 while exceeding our customers' expectations. Lead inbound operations across multiple
 shifts. Meet warehouse operational standards by implementing and monitoring daily
 production cycles.
- Mentored and coach assigned employees. Assisted with weekly employee scheduling, approval of time off requests. Trained employees on operating forklifts and other warehouse equipment as well as safety guidelines. Implemented safety policies, procedures, and training programs. Assumed leadership role in the absence of the Ops Director.
- Assisted operations in either an outbound or inbound capacity as circumstances dictate.
 Conducted safety inspections and identified and removed potential hazards. Proficient
 skill in supervising and coaching business teams. Proficient skill using Microsoft Office
 Suite in a business capacity (Outlook, Excel, and Word) and using a Windows OS PC in a
 data, email, ERP, and web browser capacity.
- Responsible for overseeing department associates, ensuring efficient operations.
 Supervised individuals performing operations to include inbound receipts/returns and inventory control functions as well as safety protocols. Container experience, RF, purchase order familiarity, put away logic and general receiving dock workflows.

03/20019-08/2020

CITY CARRIER, UNITED STATES POST OFFICE

- Routes or cases all classes of mail in sequence of delivery along an established route. Rearranges and re-labels cases as required.
- Withdraws mail from the distribution case and prepares it in sequence for efficient delivery independently or by another carrier along an established route. Prepares and separates all classes of mail to be carried by truck to relay boxes along route for subsequent delivery.
- Handles undeliverable mail in accordance with established procedures.
- Delivers and collects charges on customs, postage-due, and C.O.D. mail matter. Delivers
 and obtains receipts for registered and certain insured mail. Signs for such matter, except
 insured mail, at the post office before beginning route and accounts for it upon return by
 payments of the amounts collected and delivery of receipts taken.
- Deposits in the post office mail collected on the route upon returning from the route.
- Works professionally with other employees in the office.

09/2020-CURRENT

PHYSICAL EDUCATION INSTRUCTINAL ASSISTANT, CLARK COUNTY SCHOOL DISTRICT

- Assist the physical education teacher in performing specific duties as assigned or undertaking specialized tasks.
- Assist in establishing and maintaining standards of student behavior.
- Assist the physical education teacher in creating an environment that is conducive to learning and appropriate to the maturity and interests of the students.
- Alert the teacher to special needs of individual students.
- Provide escort and assistance to children, as necessary.
- Help maintain individual records for each student.
- Take all necessary and reasonable precautions to protect students, equipment, materials, and facilities.
- Encourage safety habits at work and organized game activities.

EDUCATION

SEPTEMBER 2021

ASSOCIATE OF ARTS WITH A CONCENTRATION IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY,

UNIVERSITY OF PHEONIX

GPA 3.12

2008

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA, LEGACY HIGH SCHOOL

AWARDS AND ACKNOWLEDGEMENTS

- CJ Pony Parts (Employee of the Month 2x, Employee of the Quarter 1x)
- Rakuten Super Logistics (Employee of the month 1x, Employee of the Year Award 1x)
- Foundation for an Independent Tomorrow (Perfect attendance Award Quarterly 3x)
- Forklift Certified/ 10+ years' experience